[{"answer": "Thought I'd get some great shots of your head gettin' blown to smithereens", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Be a prize winner", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I thought you were fighting for the Government", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "These are the Rebels", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "These are the Rebels", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "This is the that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I haven't.  Well, God dammit, I'm getting tired of memorizing who's the president of the... Republic of that place", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, he succeeded my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "But he's decided to go to that place too", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "To cover everything", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " The government accused me of using the church to hide Rebels and guns", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " This time they're right. Who are you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " I don't take sides. I take pictures", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " No", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You don't have to apologize... you're journalists", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A businessman? That sounds good. Okay, I'm a businessman", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What do I know, eh? my friend needs a victory very badly... he needs to prove to my friend that he is still winning. He thinks my friend's death is the proof he needs", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, no... the arms shipment has been delayed in that place because my friend is getting nervous", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " The Sandinistas hold the hills, the that place has everything else", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Va alli, dos o tres cuartos, doble la esquina al francotirador", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Not so simple", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm not gonna take it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Do what you want to do", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I want to be here.  With you.  What do you want", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No! I wanted my friend to be alive", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'd do it again", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No cabs", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No cabs", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Un minuto, por favor", "docId": "Under-Fire.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " They are journalists", "qsentId": 30}]